globinch.com 2010-12-08

# Globinch Privacy policy | Globinch

## [Privacy Policy](http://www.globinch.com/privacy-policy/)

Thank you for visiting **Globinch.com**

Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy.

**Collection of Information**

We respect your right to privacy and will protect it when you visit our website.The [Globinch.com](http://globinch.com/) website has contact information (including e-mail addresses) for specific sections. Should you send any correspondence to us, your email address will be used only to respond to your requests. This information is only used to fulfill your specific request, unless you give us permission to use it in another manner, for example to add you to one of our mailing lists.

**Cookie/Tracking Technology**

The Site may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. To ensure ease of use and to enhance your experience while you are visiting this site Cookies may be used.Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the Site, and understanding how visitors use the Site.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site.
  * Google’s use of the DART cookie ([DoubleClick DART cookie](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx)) enables it to serve ads to Globinch users based on their visit to Globinch and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy.](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices.

**Privacy Contact Information**

If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us using Feedback Form

We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted.
